I Wanna Dance with Somebody (Who Loves Me)
Huh
Yeah
Wooh
Hey yeah
Huh Ooh yeah
Uh huh
Yeah
I want to dance
Clock strikes upon the hour and the sun begins to fade
Still enough time to figure out how to chase my blues away
I've done alright up 'till now it's the light of day that shows me how
And when the night falls the loneliness calls
Oh I wanna dance with somebody
I wanna feel the heat with somebody
Yeah I wanna dance with somebody with somebody who loves me
Oh I wanna dance with somebody
I wanna feel the heat with somebody
Yeah I wanna dance with somebody with somebody who loves me
I've been in love and lost my senses spinning through the town
Sooner or later the fever ends and
I wind up feeling down
I need a man who'll take a chance on a love that burns hot enough to last
So when the night falls my lonely heart calls
Oh I wanna dance with somebody
I wanna feel the heat with somebody
Yeah I wanna dance with somebody with somebody who loves me
Oh I wanna dance with somebody
I wanna feel the heat
Yeah I wanna dance with somebody with somebody who loves me
Somebody who loves me yeah
To hold me in his arms, oh
I need a man who'll take a chance
On a love that burns hot enough to last
So when the night falls my lonely heart calls
I wanna dance with somebody
I wanna feel the heat with somebody
Yeah I wanna dance with somebody with somebody who loves me
I wanna dance with somebody
I wanna feel the heat with somebody
Yeah I wanna dance with somebody with somebody who loves me
Ooh ooh, ooh
Come on, baby, ha-ha-ha-ha
Ooh, yeah
Now get with this, ha-ha-ha
Whoa oh oh oh oh
Don't you wanna dance with me baby?
Don't you wanna dance with me boy?
Oh, don't you wanna dance with me baby?
With somebody who loves me
Don't you wanna dance?
Say you wanna dance?
Uh-huh
With somebody who loves me
Ooh ooh ooh